Rise up.
Pacific Rim: Uprising is a action, fantasy, science
fiction film directed by Steven S. DeKnight.
It has been ten years since The Battle of the Breach
and the oceans are still, but restless.
Vindicated by the victory at the Breach, the Jaeger program has evolved
into the most powerful global defense force in human history.
The PPDC now calls upon the best and brightest to rise up and become the
next generation of heroes when the Kaiju threat returns.
Jake Pentecost, played by John Boyega.
Nate Lambert, played by Scott Eastwood.
Amara Namani, played by Cailee Spaeny.
Liwen Shao, played by Jing Tian.
Mako Mori, played by Rinko Kikuchi.
Dr. Hermann Gottlieb, played by Burn Gorman.
Pacific Rim Uprising is a 2018 American monster action
film, the sequel to Pacific Rim (2013).
The film was directed by Steven S.
DeKnight, and written by DeKnight, Emily Carmichael, Kira Snyder, and T.
The ensemble cast includes John Boyega, Scott Eastwood, Cailee Spaeny, Jing Tian, Adria Arjona and Zhang
Jin, with Rinko Kikuchi, Charlie Day, and Burn Gorman returning from the original film.
Set ten years after the events of the first film, Pacific Rim Uprising sees former pilot and Marshal Stacker
Pentecost's son, Jake, returning to the Pan Pacific Defense Corps to stop a renewed Kaiju threat.
Principal photography began in November 2016 in Queensland, Australia.
Pacific Rim Uprising premiered in Hollywood, on March 15, 2018, and was
released in the United States on March 23, by Universal Pictures.
It received mixed reviews from critics.
With a gross of $291 million, it was considered a box-office disappointment.
It was followed by an animated television series in 2021.
The film explores themes of mind control, race
against time, japan, army, monster.
The tone is thought_provoking.